# ASTHA JAIN

Currently pursuing MCA from Thapar University with CGPA 8.17 till current semester. Ambitious, always ready to learn, gain new experience and utilize my interpersonal skills to achieve organizational goals. Interested in working in the field of DevOps, Software Testing and Analysis.





ajain1\_mca21@thapar.edu



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ Asthaajain/



https://github.com/Asthaajain



+91 8383077823



Delhi, India

## SKILLS

- Front End Coding (HTML, JS, CSS)
- C++ and Java
- Database (SQL)
- Management Skills
- On page SEO
- Wordpress
- Graphic Design
- Effective Communication

### EDUCATION

#### X

Bharat National Public School

2015 - 2016

7.8 CGPA

#### XII

Bharat National Public School

2017 - 2018

72.6%

#### **BCA**

GGS Indraprastha University, Delhi

2018 - 2021

9.00 CGPA

#### MCA

Thapar Institute of Engineering and Technology

2021 - 2023

8.17 CGPA

## EXPERIENCE

#### CITY AMBIANCE MONITOR

working

#### Python - Machine Learning, Mysql, ...

Rating cities via different parameters ( crime, weather, politics, etc.), fetching news from RSS feeds and training accordingly.

#### **TOUR MANAGER: LET'S SET GO**

2022

#### HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, php, SQL

A website which allows travellers to see or share details necessary for an excursion like Hotel expenses, fuel expenses, stay locations, things to buy, etc. all in one place. The expense calculator helps groups share expenses. Travellers are able to communicate with the chat feature. Tour guides would register and will be available for booking.

# CAMS: AN ANNOTATED CORPUS FOR CAUSAL ANALYSIS OF MENTAL HEALTH ISSUES IN SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS

2021-2022

Research Paper in LREC Conference, worked as an annotator.

#### ANALYSIS AND PREDICTION OF COVID DATA

2020-2021

#### **Python - Machine Learning**

By using real-time covid data it analyzes the data using SVM and Linear Regression and trains itself from previous data and predicts the further number of cases.

# MACHINE LEARNING: INTRODUCTION, TYPES AND APPLICATIONS

2020

Research Paper in IITM Journal of Information Technology

#### **BILL MANAGMENT SYSTEM**

2017

#### C++

Developed a bill management system which shows the items to be added and sums the amount and gives the receipt after discount using file management system in C++.